The Kamisato Clan is just one of countless families in Inazuma
ตระกูลคามิซาโตะเป็นเพียงหนึ่งในตระกูลที่มีนับไม่ถ้วนในอินาสึมะ
Hence, there is nothing exceptional about my work
เพราะฉะนั้น งานของข้าจึงไม่มีอะไรเป็นพิเศษ
I do what must be done to ensure peace and stability for my family
ข้าทำในสิ่งที่ต้องทำ เพื่อความสงบสุข และความมั่นคงของครอบครัวข้า
At home, I am the clan head, or brother, in public I am Commissioner
อยู่ที่บ้าน ข้าเป็นผู้นำตระกูลหรือพี่ชาย พออยู่ข้างนอก ข้าคือข้าราชการ
But ultimately, I am just a normal person
แต่สุดท้าย... ข้าก็เป็นเพียงแค่คนธรรมดาคนนึง
When work is busy, I don't return home for days at a time
ในช่วงที่งานยุ่งมากๆ ตัวข้าเองก็ไม่ได้กลับบ้านหลายวัน
Once the present problems are resolved, there are still future dangers to prevent
เมื่อแก้ไขปัญหาในปัจจุบันได้แล้ว ก็ยังมีภัยในอนาคตที่ต้องป้องกันอีก
This may sound vainglorious, but...
บางทีนี่อาจจะฟังดูไร้สาระ
I do what I do so that everyone has a home to go back to
แต่ข้าก็แค่ทำในสิ่งที่... จะทำให้ทุกคนได้มีบ้านให้กลับ
Huh... Most inconvenient... Time to find shelter
เฮ้อ... แบบนี้ก็ลำบากล่ะสิ... ถึงเวลาหาที่หลบฝนแล้วล่ะ
Hmm?
หืม?
Huh? Hello, my lord!
อ้าว? ท่านผู้นำตระกูลนี่!
What a surprise to run into you here, Ayato
น่าแปลกใจมากเลยที่ได้พบท่านพี่อายาโตะที่นี่
One second, I'll go start some tea
รอสักครู่ ข้าจะไปเตรียมชามาให้
Taroumaru, come on boy, down you go
ทาโระมารุ เด็กดี ลงไปก่อนนะ
Hey, c'mon, you need to let me stand up...
นี่ ไม่เอาน่า ทำแบบนี้ข้าก็ลุกไม่ได้สิ
My goodness, you're in high spirits. Thought you'd have a party without me?
แหม ดูพวกเจ้าสิ กำลังสนุกสนานกันเชียวนะ แอบจัดงานเลี้ยงลับหลังข้าเหรอ?
No, actually, we came here to make some plans for your birthd—
ไม่ จริง ๆ แล้ว พวกเรากำลังวางแผนงานวันเกิ...
Ahem, my lady...
อะแฮ่ม คุณหนู...
Hahahaha, so that's it
ฮ่าๆๆๆ อย่างนี้นี่เอง
Mm... the chance to work, and to live life
อืม... ทั้งเส้นทางการทำงานและการใช้ชีวิต
For the sake of these, people will draw their blade
เพื่อปกป้องสิ่งเหล่านี้ ผู้คนจึงต้องชักดาบออกมา